<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grace Baptist Ministries</title>
    <link>http://gbm.sg/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Grace Baptist Ministries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gbm.sg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Groups</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/connect-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/connect-groups/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Connect groups are small groups of 6-12 people who gather on a regular basis, usually at someone&amp;rsquo;s home.
Who is it for? Connect groups are made of church members, regulars and people who are interested to find out more about the christian faith.
Can I visit a few different groups before deciding on one? Yes, we understand that you may want to visit more than one group before deciding on the best one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/ministries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/ministries/</guid>
      <description>Discipleship, Evangelism &amp;amp; Community  Youth Ministry   Young Adults Ministry  Ladies Fellowship  Evangelism  Children  GBM Kids   Music, Media &amp;amp; Support  Choir Instrumentalists Media Ministry Technology Communications  Learning  Faith Bible Institute (FBI)    About Us Find out more about our history and the path that has led us here today.
Learn more    Connect Groups The connect groups are where we meet up to get to know God better in a small and safe group setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Beliefs</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/our-beliefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/our-beliefs/</guid>
      <description>This is the scriptural basis for our belief. To read about our philosophy of ministry instead, go here
1. The Holy Bible We believe that the Holy Bible was written by men supernaturally inspired by God; that it has truth without any admixture of error for its matter; and therefore is, and shall remain to the end of age, the only complete and final revelation of the will of God to man; the true centre of Christian union, and the supreme standard by which all human conduct, creeds and opinions should be tried.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Staff</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/our-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/our-staff/</guid>
      <description>Senior Pastor Christopher Chern  Senior Pastor Christopher Chern    Born in Singapore and raised in Taoism, I was very religious and joined my parents in their beliefs. I would visit the temple, ask for blessings from those gods, and wear amulets and idols for protection. In 1974, I was saved through the witness of a schoolmate who brought me to a Bible study when I was in Secondary 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Ministry</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/philosophy-of-ministry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/philosophy-of-ministry/</guid>
      <description>This is our philosophy of ministry. To read about the scriptural basis for our belief instead, go here
Our Core Values  We believe that the Bible is God’s Word to His people and is the only foundation for our faith and practice. We believe that worship is the duty of all man. We believe that a church is built on strong families and marriages. We strive to excellence in our youth and children’s programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit Us</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/visit-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/visit-us/</guid>
      <description>Regular activities  Sunday Service - Sundays 10am Chinese Bible Study - Tuesdays 10am Story of Hope - Please Contact Us for Next Available Series  Transport Directions We recommend finding a route using google maps.
Address 146B Paya Lebar Road #05-01 Singapore 409017 map
Bus Routes There are 2 nearby bus stops with the following buses
8, 22, 24, 28, 43, 70, 76, 80, 158, 70M
8, 22, 61, 63, 65, 66, 63M</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://gbm.sg/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gbm.sg/about-us/</guid>
      <description>A Brief History Grace Baptist Ministries (GBM) is founded from a merger of two church bodies. The first group, Open Bible Baptist Church (OBBC), was founded on 25 Mar 1994 under the pastoral leadership of Pastor Pat Delaney. From its humble beginnings in the home of Pastor Pat with just 2 others in 1989, the Lord brought 10 others by the time of its founding. The church continued to grow through the years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>